btls.com 2003-04-12

# WXTB-FM

Untitled Document

|  |   
---|---  
  
Revised: 2.6.02 

PRIVACY STATEMENT

This site "www.98rock.com" is owned by Clear Channel Communications, Inc., and is part of the Clear Channel family of companies which includes other quality entertainment brands such as broadcast and Internet radio stations, television stations, Clear Channel Entertainment, and the Premiere Radio Network (collectively referred to hereinafter as "we" or "this site"). This statement informs you of Clear Channel's practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information. Personal information is information that allows us to contact you (such as e-mail address, home address, or telephone number) or other information that, when linked to your name or contact information, allows us to personalize your visit to our site by providing you with information that suits your interests. 

Clear Channel is the owner of this website and retains all ownership rights to the information collected at this site. Clear Channel reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove provisions of this Privacy Statement. Any changes to this Statement will be posted here, and we encourage you to check back from time to time.

Personalization

Although you may use many features of this site without completing a registration or sign up form, visitors who do register and/or sign up for special services may have access to additional features of the site and are more likely to receive information suited to their interests. For example, a registered user is eligible for additional services provided by this website such as listener clubs and personalized content. Our registration and special services sign up forms may ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age). You must provide the information in order to receive the benefits of registration or of the special service. 

We may use the contact information that you give us to better tailor your website experience to your interests, and to send you information about Clear Channel and its services as well as promotional material on behalf of some of our partners. We use other information that you provide to us to show you content in which you may be interested and to display the content according to your preferences. We will also share this information within the Clear Channel family in order to enhance your experience on this and other Clear Channel websites. 

In addition, we may share this information with advertisers or other third parties that are not part of the Clear Channel family on an aggregate or other basis that does not disclose your identity or contact information. 

Online Surveys/Contests

From time to time, we may conduct online surveys and contests. These ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age). We may use this contact information from our surveys and contests to provide you with information about our company and promotional material on behalf of some of our partners, and to contact you when necessary. 

Supplemental Information

To enhance Clear Channel's ability to tailor this site to your preferences, we may combine information that you provide us on registration and other online sign up forms with other information about you that we may obtain. We do not share that information with any other party.

Shopping/Commercial Services

This Clear Channel site may offer shopping services, which may be offered by us or by a firm that operates a store under contract with us. If our site offers shopping or other commercial services, you will use a customer order form to request information, products, and services. The order form will ask you to give us contact information (like name or email address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like zip code or age).

We will use the financial information that you provide to bill you for products and services. By giving our site your credit card and related personal information, you are authorizing our store to give that information to the merchant and credit card company in order to confirm and fulfill your order.

We will use contact information from the order form to fulfill your orders. We may also use contact data to get in touch with you when necessary. We will not otherwise use or distribute your financial information without your prior approval. 

Public Forums 

This site may make available chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups. Please remember that any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Third Parties

From time to time we may enter into a special relationship with another company that is not owned by Clear Channel to provide additional features at this site. These special relationships may include "powered by" partners, business partners, sponsors, and co-branded sites (referred to here as "co-branded pages"). These might include, for example, pages that share our name and that of another entity, such as TicketMaster. 

You should look for a specific privacy statement on any such co-branded page. Any personal information that you provide when signing up at one of these co-branded pages may be shared with our third party partner. You should also check our partner's website for information regarding its privacy policies. 

In addition, we may share any of the information collected from you with these other non-Clear Channel companies on an aggregate basis. The aggregated information is not linked to any information that can identify you. 

IP Address

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personal information.

Cookies

This Clear Channel site may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Cookies reside on your computer, and help our website to recognize your computer's browser as a previous visitor. This information allows us to customize delivery of information. For example, our site may use cookies to save and remember registration information or preferences that you may have set while you were browsing the site, to keep track of your shopping cart, to ensure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We use cookies only to gather information as indicated in this policy. 

In addition, on occasion our site may also set a "session cookie" which cookie helps us administer the site. A session cookie expires when you close your browser, and does not retain any information about you after it expires. 

Log Files

We may use IP addresses to administer the site, to analyze trends, track users' webpage movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

Banner Advertising

We license ad-server software from another company to place banner advertising on our sites. All of the data provided and generated by the ad-server software remains in our possession, and no data is transferred to the licensor of the software. This feature of our site may, on occasion, set "cookies" on your computer. Any information collected or stored by the ad-service or the cookie is treated in the same manner as other information as described in this statement. 

Children's Personal Information 

Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act:

· This site does NOT collect, use, or disclose personal information (including online contact information) of children under the age of 13. 

· In the event that a child under the age of 13 attempts to register on our site, we will NOT accept the registration and will delete information received from the child. 

· In the event that a child posts personal information in a public forum such as a chat room, we will attempt to delete that information once we become aware of it. 

Your Choices

This Clear Channel site provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from us and our special relationship partners. As explained above, if you choose not to provide us with information sought on registration or sign up forms, it is possible that you will not be able to access or use certain features of our site. If you do choose to opt-out of such e-mail communications, you may:

· Modify your registered user information on our website; or  
· Send an email to [Clear Channel Radio Interactive Support](mailto:webservices@clearchannel.com)  
· Click **HERE**

Access to Personal Information

Clear Channel gives you the opportunity to modify or remove personal information that you have provided to us. You may do so by modifying your password-protected registered user information on our website. 

Security of Your Personal Information

Clear Channel employs reasonable security measures consistent with standard industry practice, for information collected through this website. We believe that we have adequate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information that we collect on our website. We also use internal protections to limit access to users' personal information to only those employees who need the information to perform a specific job.

Sale or Merger 

If this site is sold to, or merges with, another company not owned by Clear Channel, you should expect that some or all of the information collected from this website may be transferred to the buyer/surviving company. If so, Clear Channel will seek to obligate the acquiring company to use any personal information transferred by this site in a manner consistent with this statement, but cannot guarantee that it will be able to impose that requirement or that the acquiring company will comply.

Legal Process

You should be aware that Clear Channel may be required to disclose your personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, such as in court or regulatory proceedings. 

Links

This site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites. You should check the Privacy Statement of the website sponsor when linking to other sites. 

Contacting the Website 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact [Clear Channel Radio Interactive Support](mailto:%20webservices@clearchannel.com?subject=WXTB-FM%27s%20Privacy%20Statement%20Link). 

Leased Content 

Neither S&P nor any third-party licensor shall have any liability for the accuracy or completeness of the this service or any component thereof or for delays, unauthenticity, omissions or other defects therein nor for any claims or losses arising therefrom or occasioned thereby, including without limitation any lost profits, indirect, special or consequential damages. Either S&P or third-party licensors have exclusive proprietary rights in the information received via the service. Customer, end-user or visitor, as applicable, shall not use or permit anyone to use the information provided through the service for any unlawful or unauthorized purpose. Customer, end user, or visitor, as applicable, is not authorized or permitted to furnish such information to any person or firm for reuse or retransmission without prior written approval of the source of such information. Provision of the information on the service is subject to termination in the event that any agreement between a third-party licensor and a provider of information distributed through the service is terminated in accordance with its terms. Third-party licensor and its subsidiaries, affiliates, information providers and content partners shall have no liability for investment decisions based on the information provided hereby. 

Users may not download any images provided by Getty Images for any purpose other than personal, noncommercial use. Republication, retransmission, reproduction or other use of these images is strictly prohibited. EUROPEAN UNION AND OTHER FOREIGN NATIONS 

This Clear Channel website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States of America and is intended for the enjoyment of residents of the United States. Clear Channel makes no representation that this website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of other nations. By using this site, visitors from outside of the United States acknowledge that this site is subject to U.S. law and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.
